That’s right.
I am the Godfather.
Hahaha!
If you’re the Godfather,
then I’m his goddamn brother!
I'm feeling generous.
Get out now, or-
You’re dead.
Kill him!
You!
You! you dared attack
someone from the Sovereign Sanctum?!
Just wait!
I'll have the Holy
Knight come and end you!
Good.
I’ll wait.
My lord, you're finally here!
Who dares cause
trouble in my territory?
That would be me.
G-Godfather!
You've done well.
He's the only
one in all of
Golantis who dared
say he'd kill me.
How dare you show
disrespect to the Godfather!
Die!
I failed to keep
order in my territory.
I await your punishment, Godfather.
Return every coin
of money they took.
Then report to the Holy Court
for your own punishment.
Yes, my lord!
Well, our little trip got ruined.
Let’s go home.
Go home to
do what, my lord?
What do you think?
Fine.
Let's go home...
and make you a little Godfather.